So I just wanted to say that I have not watched my Surrounded yet, but I've seen your comments and people have been texting me and it was a very out of body experience.
Like once I get into that kind of mode, I am being more so an antenna and a transmitter of my guides.
And so I kind of like don't have any recollection of how it how it went and after.
And so I've been having a lot of anxiety about it and I care so deeply about being a contributor to the direction of change for the better in this world, which is why when I feel like I've fallen short of that, like I really, really beat myself up.
Um, and so far you guys's responses have have affirmed that I've done what I was supposed to do in this particular instance.
I'll be talking about this on my P-A-T-R-E-O-N.
I can't say the actual word because then Instagram will suppress this video, but I will be watching it in full this evening at 7 p.m. at the first link in my bio.
So if you're interested in seeing more, um, and getting more insight and, you know, having a watch with me experience that, uh, enriches us all go to the first link in my bio.
But even if you don't, um, I do appreciate any of you all who have taken the time to watch it and who have provided commentary and who have encouraged me.
I appreciate it. Thank you.